[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Are you doing well at his house?
Pretty good.
That's good.
Master.
Don't go.
Do you know her?
She is Director Wang's newly wedded third concubine,
Feiyan's sister,
and one of Yuehaitang's people.
[A Prophet]
[Episode 11]
Director, you were born into one family and raised in another.
What do you mean?
The ones who raised you are not your biological parents.
Go on.
There is a river or a pond
south of your ancestral home.
That's why you managed to become an official.
Keep divining.
If you don't tell me whether I'm right or wrong, I won't dare to say more.
You're right.
There was a pond.
But it dried up during a severe drought.
You have taken all the good feng shui.
When you became an official, the water naturally disappeared.
These are all verifiable.
Tell me something others don't know.
There's a piece of shrapnel three inches below your Dantian.
It seems you're called the Iron Plate Fortune Teller
for a good reason.
I admit I still can't quite figure out
this whole affair you mentioned.
Let's talk in private.
All of you, get out.
Director...
Get out, get out.
You are brilliant, Master.
We almost
fell into Fan Jialie's trap.
I'll deal with that guy
sooner or later.
He's still inexperienced.
How are the preparations
for the salvation ritual going?
Shangguan Chengming is planning to gather
the people by the river and hold
an altar ritual on July 15th.
Get my outfit ready.
I'll perform the ritual when the time comes.
Is that appropriate?
We're in the teeth of the storm right now.
Just let that kid do it.
This represents the Tianxiang Sect.
He's not qualified for it.
Do you really plan to keep him in Tianxiang Sect?
Don't you think this kid is quite interesting?
He's alright.
I just think
he doesn't deserve you treating him so well.
Back then, people also advised me
not to treat you so well.
[The show begins]
[Linjiang Pier]
Start the ritual.
Why are you here?
Liang.
Can we skip it today?
This mission is important. I have to go.
I'm afraid the Plum Blossom Sect will come to cause trouble.
If you're afraid of dying, go home and feed the pigs.
Let go.
Father.
Rest in peace.
I miss you.
Please, gods, bless my mother
with a full recovery
and a long life.
God bless.
Let me have a child this year.
My child.
Be born into a good family in your next life
so you won't go hungry.
Peace and safety
year after year.
May our family be safe,
may everything go smoothly,
and may it all end well.
Bless my son with good health
and a life free of illness.
Liang.
Bro.
Easy, easy.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sect Master.
Sit down, everyone.
Sit.
Sect Master, why are you here?
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
You expected
something to happen tonight, didn't you?
You crashed the Plum Blossom Sect's setup
and offended them.
Did you think they'd let it go?
We should have handed you over to them.
I will take responsibility for my own actions.
It's not too late to hand me over now.
This is no longer just your problem.
We can't
suffer this loss for nothing.
I had a great time today.
I'll come again next time.
As for this Fan Jialie,
we have already figured him out.
This guy
makes dirty money,
has wide influence,
is treacherous and cunning,
and never leaves a trace.
Seventh Brother and I have also uncovered some information.
Their legitimate businesses
are all under his biological son...
Fan Zhehan.
Yes.
Under Fan Zhehan's name.
But Fan Zhehan
is a hopeless case.
He spends all day womanizing.
In short,
the Fan family's dirty money
all goes through the secret accounts of Shunxiang Teahouse.
My friends at the teahouse also told me
that Fan Jialie has an illegitimate son
named Fan Xinze.
He was born to a prostitute,
so his father doesn't like him
and made him a waiter at the teahouse.
Fan Zhehan also bullies him often.
This Fan Jialie is a bastard.
His eldest son
is also a bastard.
Doesn't he treat his eldest son like a treasure?
Let's cut off
his lifeline.
Cut off his family jewels?
Yan can do this job just fine.
As the saying goes, lust is a knife above the head.
If Yan takes action,
she can solve it with two fingers.
You talk too much.
Are you angry?
Just kidding.
Fan Jialie has harmed many people these years.
He even dared to attack the people of the Tianxiang Sect.
Now,
it's not just for the members of the Tianxiang Sect,
but also for the people of Yucheng.
So,
we must deal with him.
Feiyan.
Master.
Since it's what everyone hopes,
then Fan Zhehan...
is in your hands.
Please.
Don't worry, Master.
Let's toast to the Fifth Batou.
Cheers.
To a successful start.
Let's eat.
Liu.
Meatballs.
Happy birthday.
This is the first time someone
has prepared longevity noodles for me.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Everything said during the setup was fake.
Forget it.
Actually,
I don't even know
when my birthday is.
Dealing with Fan Jialie
must be very troublesome, right?
I can help you.
I have a plan...
Didn't you say today is my birthday?
Then why don't
I make a wish?
I hope that
you will not participate in any of the Tianxiang Sect's schemes
in the future.
Young Master Fan, you're here.
Please come in.
Young Master Fan.
Miss Xiaoyun has gotten prettier.
Come on.
Young Master Fan, why are you so late today?
The girls are all waiting for you.
Madam Sang.
I heard you have a new
female Fortune-teller from Pujiang.
Indeed.
Mr. Fan, you really are
well-informed.
Our Miss Wantang
is making her debut here
tonight.
Young Master Fan.
Do you also want to join the tea gathering?
Exactly.
I'm booking Miss Wantang for tonight.
I want to invite her to see the night view of Yucheng.
You think you can just book her like that?
Do you know what first come, first served means?
Where did this little punk come from?
How dare you challenge me in Yucheng?
I offer one hundred.
You reek of poverty.
Get out of the way.
Young Master Fan.
Miss Wantang
is already friends with this gentleman.
This has nothing to do with money.
Nothing.
Friendship is priceless.
I get it.
You want more money.
Madam Sang.
I wonder if this gold bar
is enough?
Is that all you've got?
I offer 3 gold bars.
Where did this guy come from?
Do you know who I am?
I really don't know.
Why don't
you tell me in detail?
Young Master.
Young Master,
don't stoop to his level.
Master already dislikes you
coming to such places.
You talk too much.
Get lost.
Just you wait.
Yinlian!
Where is Yinlian?
Congratulations, young master.
Congratulations on winning the beauty.
I'll prepare things for you.
Why did you buy this?
It's too expensive.
Aren't you saving money to buy my freedom?
Don't worry, Yinlian.
I've already talked to Madam Sang.
This little bit won't matter.
Once I've saved up enough money,
I'll get you out of here.
Then we can be together.
Young Master.
There's a guest inside.
I'm pissed off today
because of you.
Get out of my way.
I was wondering which VIP was here.
So it's you sneaking around here.
Young Master Fan,
what brings you here today?
Madam Sang, what's with the arrangement?
A guest like Young Master Fan
should be in the VIP room.
Young Master Fan.
Get out of my way.
I wanted
to come here.
Yinlian.
Did you miss me?
Young Master Fan.
When you're out,
you should follow the rule of first come, first served.
Rules?
You're talking to me about rules?
Fine.
Then today,
I'll teach you about rules.
There is a difference between the legitimate and the illegitimate.
Moreover,
you're not even considered illegitimate.
Back then, to gamble on that hand of cards,
you lost everything
and lived off women.
What?
Now you're playing the romantic here?
No wonder
you get so excited when you see a whore.
I forgot.
Your mother
came from here, didn't she?
Look, we're brothers.
How can we get mad over a whore?
Right?
Come, come.
You...
Can just sit here.
And you...
Come with me.
Young Master!
You get called Mr. Fan once,
and you think you're part of the Fan family?
You son of a whore.
In this lifetime,
don't ever think about entering the Fan family's genealogy.
You're just like your whore mother,
only fit to beg for mercy
and live like a dog.
I told you not to come, but you insisted.
I'm not here for pleasure.
I'm here on business.
Give me some water.
The drinks here
are for entertaining guests.
This...
You can't drink this.
If there's poison in this wine,
I can smell it.
Good wine.
Very thirst-quenching.
You can detect poison by scent.
But what if there's
something else in this wine?
For example,
an aphrodisiac?
Really?
I wonder.
You'll know soon enough.
Wait.
Weren't you going to drug that Fan brat?
What kind of move is this?
I wanted to make him anxious.
Make him want it,
but unable to have it.
Water.
Give me water.
The one who saved me at Nanxi River back then,
was it you?
Master Du.
Why are you here in the middle of the night?
Where are those two kids?
That's not for you to ask.
Before I entered the Wang family,
you told me
I could leave after getting the money.
Now you want to kill someone?
Why do you never learn your lesson?
I warned you.
In the setup, you are no longer yourself.
Don't get emotionally involved with the mark.
Master Du.
Please let those two kids go.
Can you?
After acting for a few days,
do you really think you're a chaste and righteous woman?
Have you forgotten the rules?
But the Sect Master's rule is no killing.
I didn't hear what you just said.
The Sect Master's rule is no killing...
You've learned to talk back.
Don't think just because the Sect Master values you,
you can be disrespectful to me.
You little bitches from Yuehaitang
are just objects in our hands
to be ordered around.
Do objects have the right to speak?
Was it you?
Yes.
You saved me.
Aren't you afraid of ruining the setup?
I already saved you.
What is there to be afraid of?
Tell me.
What exactly do you want to do?
Leave Fan Zhehan alone.
I'll deal with that illegitimate son.
A legitimate son is a treasure.
An illegitimate son is just a weed.
I want the treasure,
not the weed.
Even though this weed seems worthless,
in this setup,
he is a treasure.
[Wanli Gambling House]
Have fun, boss.
I'm done playing. I lose every day.
I'm never coming back.
Deal again.
I don't know whose bad luck rubbed off on me.
I haven't won a single hand all night.
I'm so mad.
Come on.
Wait.
Let me do it.
Seven.
Heaven, Earth, Tiger Head.
So big.
Three and six make a goose.
Top and bottom lose; Heaven wins.
Are you going to jinx me all night?
Brother.
What?
Do me a favor.
Sit here and don't move.
Don't ruin my feng shui.
I'll give you half
of all my winnings tonight.
Let's continue.
Bets placed, hands off.
For me?
Come on, blow on it.
Blow what?
Blow some of your magic breath on it.
You're crazy.
What?
A nine-harmony win?
Such a big hand.
How is that possible?
Really?
Pay up.
Brother.
Tonight, we are the kings of the room.
I'm going to establish my dominance with this hand.
Just tell me, for this hand,
do we go all out?
All out!
[Chunfeng House]
Sect Master wants to know how your plan is going.
I heard
Shangguan Chengming
meddled in this.
There was a slight hiccup,
but no harm was done.
The mark has taken the bait.
Sect Master
is kind-hearted.
But you need to see things clearly.
Shangguan Chengming
has wild ambitions.
Be careful not to get bitten by him.
Have some tea before you go.
Get out of here right now!
Get out!
I can walk by myself.
Bro.
My name is Fan Xinze.
What's your name?
Me?
My name is Shangguan Chengming.
I'm sorry
for losing all your capital.
No worries.
Just come with me to a place.
Once I get my capital back,
we'll continue.
We're here.
Mr. Shangguan.
You came here...
To get money?
Fan.
Wait for me here for one night.
Tomorrow morning,
I will definitely get the money.
Mr. Jing?
Mr. Shangguan.
What happened to you?
I'm fine.
Let me go back and rest for two days.
I'll fight with you again when I return.
Definitely.
For sure.
Can you handle it?
Even if it costs my life,
I must stand with Fan
to make a comeback.
Okay.
Take care. I'll get going.
Alright.
Get some good rest.
See you.
Mr. Shangguan, what did you do?
Are you okay?
Let's keep going.
Win! Win!
I think it will definitely be fine this time.
Mr. Shangguan, you should nourish yourself.
Eat more and make yourself at home.
Don't hold back.
Fan, you run a teahouse business?
I'm watching this place for someone.
I heard
the owner of this teahouse is Director Fan.
That's my father.
Fan,
so you are from the Fan family.
I've even met your brother, Eldest Young Master Fan.
He's not my brother.
I understand.
Every family has its own problems.
Here.
Young Master.
Here is the chicken soup you asked me to simmer.
Go do your work. I'll serve this myself.
You're too kind. There's too much food to finish.
I prepared this especially for you while you were resting.
Thank you.
Thank you, Fan.
It smells so good.
Mr. Shangguan.
You made so much money overnight.
How did you do it?
I mean no offense.
I just also want to earn more
and continue winning with you.
We already treat each other like bros.
As for this matter...
Well, this matter...
It's mainly bad for your health.
This matter
is related to health?
What do you mean?
You could say it is,
but you could also say it isn't.
My current blessings are all thanks to
my past-life wealth.
Past-life wealth?
The so-called past-life wealth
is the wealth accumulated by each family
over countless past lives.
The people of this family
must constantly accumulate virtue and do good deeds
to withdraw it.
Half a year ago, at Yunhe Temple,
I met an otherworldly master.
He was the one who helped me withdraw it.
However, karma and reincarnation are predestined.
The more past-life wealth you withdraw,
the more disasters you will face in this life.
Mr. Shangguan,
what you're saying is so mysterious.
You're not making fun of me, are you?
Disasters?
What kind of disasters?
Master Mei told me
that the female Fortune-teller from Pujiang
is probably a fraud.
A female fraud?
What can she cheat me out of?
My body?
If you and that girl don't get intimate,
it's fine.
But if you have any improper thoughts,
that girl
will definitely say she is cursed by a demon.
If you sleep with her, Young Master Fan,
they will say you are cursed by a demon.
Master Mei, you're exaggerating.
She's just a woman.
If she can really play so many tricks,
I ought to see her myself.
[Chunfeng House]
Be careful, Young Master.
This floor
only trips reckless people.
Miss Wantang,
you put this incense burner right in the doorway.
Does this mean I'm not welcome?
How could that be?
Don't just stand there, Young Master.
Come and sit.
Have a cup of tea
to calm your nerves.
Miss Wantang, you're not trying to say
that we're only having tea
and that I can't get close to you, are you?
You are an honored guest
from a prestigious family.
I will naturally entertain you well.
It's just that...
You wouldn't make things
too difficult or me, would you?
I've already paid double.
If you think it's not enough,
I can add more.
Young Master.
You've already given enough money.
It's just that...
Miss Wantang, you're not trying to say
that you're cursed by a demon,
and if I get close,
something bad will happen to me, are you?
Actually, I don't believe in those things either.
I did indeed use
the tea-session-only excuse
to avoid many stinky men I look down on.
However,
meeting a noble person like Mr. Fan tonight,
I am
willing to make an exception.
Then...
Young Master.
Don't be so impatient.
Please sit here and rest for a while.
I still
need to make some preparations.
Then go prepare quickly.
Miss Wantang,
what new trick from Pujiang is this?
You don't understand.
I'm doing all this
for your sake.
For my sake?
Then hurry over here
and let me admire you.
Mr. Fan.
No need to rush.
Look at all that sweat.
Let me wipe it for you.
Are you alright, Mr. Fan?
I'm fine.
Young Master.
Actually, I'm doing all this
because I'm afraid something might happen to you.
I don't want to get into a lawsuit later.
I can't bear that responsibility.
What lawsuit?
You don't know, Mr. Fan.
Years ago, an old Fortune-teller
said I was under a demonic spell.
He also said that
anyone who slept with me
would die suddenly.
Who would believe that?
At first, I didn't believe it either.
But who could have thought that
on the day of my wedding
with my husband,
he...
What happened on the wedding day?
He was really killed by me.
He died, not me.
He died,
so aren't you mine now?
Mr. Fan,
why won't you listen to anything I say?
What if something happens to you?
Stop struggling.
Tonight, you are mine.
Mr. Fan,
wait a moment.
Oh my god!
What's wrong?
Get up.
Mr. Fan.
Why am I suddenly so itchy?
Why do you have so many
red rashes on your chest?
This is exactly the same
as the red rashes my husband had back then.
This...
Why are there suddenly so many red rashes?
Mr. Fan,
why don't you let me
take a look for you?
Don't.
Just stay here.
Why is it so itchy?
This is really bizarre.
Mr. Fan,
let me take a look for you.
No.
Stop.
Just stand there.
Don't come over.
It seems that
you dislike me now.
I don't dislike you.
I just don't like feeling itchy.
Today...
That's all for today.
Mr. Fan,
if you leave now,
the money won't be refunded.
Keep the money here.
I'll come back next time.
The chief ordered
to take this woman back to the residence.
Infinite blessings.
Master, we're here.
Master.
People fear accidents,
and incense fears different lengths.
This saying is indeed true.
What a pity.
What do you mean?
I just cast a hexagram.
The hexagram says
Mr. Jing is gone.
The Mr. Jing I know?
He passed away last night.
Mr. Jing?
Mr. Shangguan.
Rest well.
See you.
The guy from yesterday?
If I remember correctly,
you were brought here by Mr. Jing.
Yes.
Your friend, Mr. Jing,
withdrew too much past-life wealth.
The backlash was too heavy,
and he couldn't survive it.
Today is not a good time either.
I have to perform a ritual to send the money back.
Please come back another day.
Fan,
the Master is not available today.
Let's come back another day.
Mr. Shangguan.
Are we just leaving like this?
I haven't got the money yet.
When I first met Mr. Jing,
he was still a burly man.
Since he took his past-life wealth,
although he became rich overnight,
his body
suddenly became as thin as a rake,
and his face became haggard.
His outcome
truly proves the saying that
greed knows no bounds.
What about the money in the alchemy furnace?
The master will naturally put it back.
Mr. Jing,
you can still use it in your next life.
Fan.
I think we should just forget it.
With your body,
I'm afraid you can't handle it.
I'll just take a little.
I have an urgent need.
Are you in some kind of trouble, Fan?
A woman.
Master.
Please help him.
You are so stubborn.
Master.
Fan is taking this past-life wealth
to save someone.
Master!
Master.
Really.
My parents gave birth to me but didn't raise me.
Without this money,
I can't even afford to get a wife.
I hope you can help me.
Master.
Look,
Fan is also a poor, suffering man.
Please help him.
Bring me his Four Pillars of Destiny.
Let me take a look first.
Your Four Pillars of Destiny.
Master.
Boundless Heavenly Honor!
You are no ordinary person.
You have the most past-life wealth I've ever seen.
Come.
Follow me.
Please.
See it for yourself.
These are from our ancestors?
That's your past-life wealth in there.
Then how do I withdraw it?
[In the next episode]
I didn't expect
to come up against you, Yuehaitang Branch's grandmaster, today.
Master Mei,
you've treated me like this—
do you think the Tianxiang Sect
will let you off?
Does your Sect Master know his right-hand woman
is planning an uprising?
Why did you kill Mei Xuanzi?
I can tell you the truth.
But do you dare hear it?
I dare.